A Guide to the Papers of William Faulkner, 1929-1962
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of William Faulkner, 1929-1962
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
9817-c
239 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mrs. Paul D. Summers, Jr., through James D. Meriwether, April 24, 1979
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in two series: I. Correspondence. II. Miscellaneous.
Contents List
- CORRESPONDENCE
  - Letter, F. C. Browkaw to Louise Bonino enclosing printed review of The Sound and the Fury,1930 Feb 21, TLS (1 p. on 1 l.)
  - Letter, "Louise" to William Faulkner regarding review clippings 1936 Jan 7, TLS (1 p. on 1 l.)
  - Letter, "Louise" to William Faulkner accompanied by a photograph (photograph item #0528)of a drawing of William Faulkner by Louise Costello 1936 Nov 9, TLS (1 p. on 1 l.)
  - Letter, Betty Hoar to Miss Oldham, accompanied by a photograph (photograph item #0529)of a picture postcard of children, including William Faulkner n.d., TNS (1 p. on 1 l.)
- MISCELLANEOUS
  - Reviews of The Sound and the Fury1929 Oct - 1930 Nov, n.d., 37 newspaper clippings
  - Reviews of Soldiers' Pay1930 Jun - Jul, 4 newspaper clippings
  - Reviews of These Thirteen1931 Sep - Nov, n.d., 25 newspaper clippings
  - Reviews of Light in August1932 Oct - 1933, n.d., 63 newspaper clippings
  - Reviews of The Reivers1962 May - Jun, n.d., 98 newspaper clippings
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding William Faulkner 1930, 1951, 1962, n.d., 9 newsclippings